

TECHINICAL SKILLS

React.JS Redux CSS Javascript HTML NodeJS SOL MongoDB

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Self-Motivated Fast learner Collaborative Communication Organized Time management

CONTACT

E: mark.mulligan.jr1@gmail.com P: 817-504-5426 W: mark-mulligan.github.io G: github.com/Mark-Mulligan

MARK MULLIGAN

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

mark.mulligan.jr1@gmail.com

817-504-5426



github.com/Mark-Mulligan



mark-mulligan.github.io



https://www.linkedin.com/in/mark-mulligan-50/

ABOUT

I am a former band director turned front end developer. I am familiar with all things react and enjoy creating amazing websites. I also have experience working on backend technologies, databases, REST APIS, and creating full stack applications.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance | 2019 - Present

 Worked with multiple clients to fulfill their vision of building a website for their personal needs or business

SMU CODING BOOTCAMP

Student | Sept 2020 - March 2021

• Graduated at the top of the cohort and achieved a 4.0 gpa

ASSISTANT BAND DIRECTOR

Frisco ISD | Sept 2018 - Present

- Experience Working in a collaborative team environment
- · Planned, coordinated, and management multiple projects

EDUCATION

SMU CODING BOOTCAMP

Southern Methodist University | 2020

BACHELOR OF ARTS, MUSIC EDUCATION

University of North Texas | 2012 - 2017 Summa Con Laude